

Projects Sales Manager BAHI TAKIEDDINE

Projects sales manager, trilingual with good experience in the building materials sales field, good handle on the technical specifications of the drywalls and ceilings systems, with proven sales targets achievement, and several reference projects in the residential, hospitality, and healthcare sectors, skilled in establishing long relationships and committed to continues self-development.

Contact

- Mob: +213 554 747 846

- Mail: takibahi07@gmail.com

- Address: Algeria

Education

Master Architecture & Technology

Training

2024: Jotun Sales Way

2023: Knauf Insulation Systems

2023: Sales Cursus/ P&P/ 192 H

2022: TOT/Pro Training/80 H

2022: Sales-Force CRM/ 72 H

2021: Knauf's Ceiling & Drywall

Personal Qualities

- Communication Skills
- Teamwork and Team Lead
- Relationships Establishing Skills
- Adaptability and Flexibility

Expertise

- Accounts Management.
- Commercial Negotiations
- Technical Knowledge
- Area Sales Development

Languages

- English: Professional

- Arabic: Native Speaker

- French: Fluent

Volunteerism

- CV_UP Initiative Founder

Experience

Since Mar 2024: Sales Specialist – Jotun Paints Algeria

- Lead and expand account base by identifying potential projects and retail candidates in 10 Cities.
- Manage the orders of 08 dealers, deliveries and collection.

Nov 2021 - Feb 2024: Technical Sales Engineer - Knauf Algeria

- Identifying the projects technical needs and establishing the technical specifications.
- Preparing and conducting the commercial negotiations with customers to close at least 02 new deals/ month.
- Conducting 02 product demonstrations/ month on projects.
- Ensuring 06 customer meetings/day and input the details in CRM.
- Organize 01 Technical day/month for project owners, contractors.
- Supporting architects, consultants and designers in their projects by providing at least 10 systems specifications/month.

Jan 2021 – Oct 2021: Area Sales Manager / Oxxo Baies

- Following up closely the unpaid invoices, and ensure a collection 50% of the overdue payments/Month.
- Developing sales strategy with sales manager, and revising it according to the sales target plan achievement.
- Leading a team of 06 sales engineers to achieve sales objectives.
- Ensuring technical and sales capabilities progress of the team

Apr 2019 – Dec 2020: Area Technical Responsible / Oxxo Baies

- Respecting the deliveries deadline set with customers by collaborating with the supply chain department.
- Ensuring a good client experience by resolving the complaints.